[
  {
    "question": "What is the term for a word that has the opposite meaning of another word?",
    "answer": "Antonym",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd4f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What do we call a word that is spelled the same but has different meanings and pronunciations?",
    "answer": "Homograph",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd4f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term refers to a word formed by combining parts of other words?",
    "answer": "Compound word",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd4f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name for words that sound like the noise they describe, such as 'buzz' or 'hiss'?",
    "answer": "Onomatopoeia",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd4f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes words that are similar in meaning?",
    "answer": "Synonym",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd4f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "In French, what is the term for the verb form that expresses a completed action?",
    "answer": "Passé composé",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd50" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What do we call the accent mark used in French to indicate a rising tone?",
    "answer": "Accent aigu",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd50" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "In French grammar, what is the term for the conjunction 'and'?",
    "answer": "Et",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd50" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the French term for the part of speech that modifies a noun?",
    "answer": "Adjectif",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd50" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name for the tense used in French to express actions that will happen in the future?",
    "answer": "Futur simple",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd50" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "How would you say 'hello' in Spanish?",
    "answer": "Hola",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd51" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Spanish word for 'goodbye'?",
    "answer": "Adiós",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd51" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "How would you ask someone 'How are you?' in Spanish?",
    "answer": "¿Cómo estás?",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd51" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Spanish word for 'thank you'?",
    "answer": "Gracias",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd51" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "How would you say 'I love you' in Spanish?",
    "answer": "Te amo",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd51" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "How is the letter 'ü' pronounced in German?",
    "answer": "It is pronounced like the 'u' in 'rue'",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd52" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct pronunciation of the letter 'ä' in German?",
    "answer": "It is pronounced like the 'a' in 'cat'",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd52" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you pronounce the letter 'ö' in German?",
    "answer": "It is pronounced like the 'i' in 'bird'",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd52" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct pronunciation of the letter 'ß' in German?",
    "answer": "It is pronounced like the 's' in 'miss'",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd52" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "How is the letter 'ch' pronounced in German?",
    "answer": "It is pronounced like the 'ch' in 'loch'",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a3b0e77c7a8772fe74d9" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd52" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  }
]
